let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who scored with his hand in the 1986 World Cup quarterfinals against England?",
    answer: "Diego Maradona",
    options: [
      "Zinedine Zidane",
      "Pele",
      "Diego Maradona",
      "Ronaldo"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Ex-West Ham striker Paulo Di Canio was from which country?",
    answer: "Italy",
    options: [
      "Italy",
      "Germany",
      "Sweden",
      "Spain"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Complete the name of this former Premier League team. Charlton _____",
    answer: "Athletic",
    options: [
      "Wycombe",
      "Barnsley",
      "Wigan",
      "Athletic"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "John Terry spent his entire playing career at which club?",
    answer: "Chelsea",
    options: [
      "Manchester City",
      "Juventus",
      "Chelsea",
      "Liverpool"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "David Seaman represented which country internationally?",
    answer: "England",
    options: [
      "Germany",
      "England",
      "Hungary",
      "France"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Ex-Arsenal player Dennis Bergkamp is from which country?",
    answer: "Netherlands",
    options: [
      "England",
      "France",
      "Netherlands",
      "Italy"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Manchester United are also known as 'The Red .......'?",
    answer: "Devils",
    options: [
      "Bulls",
      "Men",
      "Kite",
      "Devils"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "In what position does Harry Kane play?",
    answer: "TStriker",
    options: [
      "Midfielder",
      "Defender",
      "Striker",
      "Goalkeeper"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "How many teams are promoted to the Premier League each season from the division below?",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "2",
      "4",
      "3",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Gareth Bale plays for which country?",
    answer: "Wales",
    options: [
      "Wales",
      "Sweden",
      "Finland",
      "Scotland"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Complete the name of this former Premier League team. Bolton _____",
    answer: "Wanderers",
    options: [
      "County",
      "Vale",
      "Wanderers",
      "City"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "David Beckham left Manchester United in 2003 to join which Spanish team?",
    answer: "Real Madrid",
    options: [
      "Atletico Madrid",
      "Real Madrid",
      "Valencia",
      "Getafe"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Former Arsenal manager Arsene Wenger is from which country?",
    answer: "France",
    options: [
      "Italy",
      "Portugal",
      "Germany",
      "France"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "David Beckham played for which MLS team in the United States?",
    answer: "LA Galaxy",
    options: [
      "Atalanta United",
      "Inter Miami",
      "LA Galaxy",
      "Orlando City"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "The city of Liverpool has two clubs in the Premier League - Liverpool & which other?",
    answer: "Everton",
    options: [
      "West Ham",
      "Crystal Palace",
      "Sheffield United",
      "Everton"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Steven Gerrard & Wayne Rooney are both from which English city?",
    answer: "Liverpool",
    options: [
      "Manchester",
      "Liverpool",
      "Swansea",
      "Bristol"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Fulham Football Club are situated in which English city?",
    answer: "London",
    options: [
      "Birmingham",
      "Leicester",
      "London",
      "Coventry"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "As of 2020, which of these teams have been relegated the most times from the Premier League?",
    answer: "Norwich City",
    options: [
      "Sunderland",
      "West Brom",
      "Norwich City",
      "Hull City"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "What type of weaponry features on the Arsenal club badge?",
    answer: "Cannon",
    options: [
      "Machine Gun",
      "Dagger",
      "Shotgun",
      "Cannon"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "What is the nickname of Arsenal Football Club?",
    answer: "The Gunners",
    options: [
      "The Gooners",
      "The Gunners",
      "The Guns",
      "The Gunner Boys"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "Which of these is a famous stand at Liverpool's Anfield stadium?",
    answer: "The Kop",
    options: [
      "The Kopp",
      "The Cop",
      "The Kops",
      "The Kop"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Which Merseyside club play at Goodison Park?",
    answer: "Everton",
    options: [
      "Everton",
      "Tranmere",
      "Southport",
      "Pilkington"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "What did Eric Cantona do in 1995 that earned him a 9 month ban from football?",
    answer: "Kung-fu kicked an opposing fan during a game",
    options: [
      "Took off his clothes during the game",
      "Punched the referee in the face",
      "Kung-fu kicked an opposing fan during a game",
      "Threw things into the crowd"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "What type of animal features on the Chelsea club badge?",
    answer: "Lion",
    options: [
      "Tiger",
      "Lion",
      "Jaguar",
      "Panther"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "Which team did Thiago Alcantara sign for in the summer of 2020?",
    answer: "Liverpool",
    options: [
      "Bayern Munich",
      "Barcelona",
      "Atletico Madrid",
      "Liverpool"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 26,
    question: "Who is the leading goal scorer in La Liga history?",
    answer: "Lionel Messi",
    options: [
      "Telmo Zarra",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Hugo Sanchez"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 27,
    question: "Who won La Liga Best Player award 2015/2016?",
    answer: "Antonio Griezmann",
    options: [
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Antonio Griezmann",
      "Cristiano Ronaldo",
      "Luis Suarez"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 28,
    question: "Which club has the highest number of trophies in spain?",
    answer: "Real Madrid",
    options: [
      "Real Madrid",
      "Barcelona",
      "Atletico Madrid",
      "Espanyol"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 29,
    question: "Messi scored his first ever hat trick against which spanish club?",
    answer: "Real Madrid",
    options: [
      "Real Betis",
      "Getafe",
      "Athletic Bilbao",
      "Real Madrid"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 30,
    question: "2010 Fifa World Cup best player named Diego Forlan who played which spanish clubs?",
    answer: "Villareal and Atletico Madrid",
    options: [
      "Villareal and Atletico Madrid",
      "Villareal and Sevilla",
      "Real Madrid and Real Sociedad",
      "Atletico Madrid and Real Betis"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 31,
    question: "Which year did Messi scored his first ever hat trick against Real Madrid?",
    answer: "2007",
    options: [
      "2009",
      "2008",
      "2007",
      "2010"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 32,
    question: "Which is the oldest club in spain?",
    answer: "Sevilla",
    options: [
      "Real Madrid",
      "Sevilla",
      "Barcelona",
      "Athletic Club"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 33,
    question: "Who has won the most number of 'Zamora Trophy' by keeping highest amount of clean sheets in La Liga history?",
    answer: "Jan Oblak",
    options: [
      "Iker Casillas",
      "Victor Valdes",
      "Mark-Andre ter Stegen",
      "Jan Oblak"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 34,
    question: "Which stadium in spain has the highest seating capacity with 99,354 seats?",
    answer: "Camp Nou",
    options: [
      "Estadio Vicente Calderon",
      "Estadio Santiago Bernabeu",
      "Camp Nou",
      "RCDE Stadium"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 35,
    question: "Who was the first Real Madrid's manager?",
    answer: "Arthur Johnson",
    options: [
      "Juande Ramos",
      "Vicente del Bosque",
      "Fabio Capello",
      "Arthur Johnson"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 36,
    question: "AC Milan was founded in December 1899. Which English city were the club's founders from?",
    answer: "Nottingham",
    options: [
      "Nottingham",
      "Birmingham",
      "Bergamo",
      "Venice"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 37,
    question: "Which club, famous for their purple shirts, were the first-ever winners of the European Cup Winners' Cup in 1961?",
    answer: "Fiorentina",
    options: [
      "Juventus",
      "Fiorentina",
      "Roma",
      "Napoli"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "In which year did AC Milan win their first Campionato?",
    answer: "1901",
    options: [
      "1901", 
      "1900",
      "1902",
      "1905"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 39,
    question: "Who was the 2001 number 1 overall pick in the draft?",
    answer: "Kwame Brown",
    options: [
      "Tyson Chandler", 
      "Pau Gasol",
      "Joe Johnson",
      "Kwame Brown"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 40,
    question: "Who won the NBA dunk contest in 2016",
    answer: "Zach Lavine",
    options: [
      "Aaron Gordon", 
      "Zach Lavine",
      "Victor Oladipo",
      "Will Barton"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 41,
    question: "Magic Johnson was inducted into the NBA Hall of Fame in what year?",
    answer: "2002",
    options: [
      "1999", 
      "2000",
      "2001",
      "2002"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 42,
    question: "How many NBA officials are in a game? ",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "3", 
      "2",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 43,
    question: "Which NBA team won eight consecutive championships from 1959 to 1966?",
    answer: "Boston Celtics",
    options: [
      "Boston Celtics", 
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Miami Heat"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 44,
    question: "Who is the Chicago Bulls mascot?",
    answer: "Benny the Bull",
    options: [
      "Lenny the Bull", 
      "Kenny the Bull",
      "Benny the Bull",
      "Penny the Bull"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 45,
    question: "What number did Michael Jordan wear when playing for the Chicago Bulls? ",
    answer: "23",
    options: [
      "43", 
      "30",
      "21",
      "23"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 46,
    question: "Which famous player is the NBA logo modelled after? ",
    answer: "Jerry West",
    options: [
      "Larry Bird", 
      "Steve Nash",
      "Jerry West",
      "Dirk Nowitzki"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 47,
    question: "Which team drafted Giannis Antetokounmpo in 2013?",
    answer: "Milwaukee Bucks",
    options: [
      "Indiana Pacers", 
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Oklohoma City Thunder",
      "Cleveland Cavaliers"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 48,
    question: "Who won the first official NBA game when it started?",
    answer: "New York Knicks",
    options: [
      "Portland Trailblazers", 
      "Brooklyn Nets",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "New York Knicks"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 49,
    question: "Who is the current NBA commissioner? ",
    answer: "Adam Silver",
    options: [
      "Larry O'Brien", 
      "Maurice Podoloff",
      "Adam Silver",
      "David Stern"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 50,
    question: "Micheal Jordan famously retired from basketball in 1993. What sport did he go on to play instead? ",
    answer: "Baseball",
    options: [
      "Baseball", 
      "Tennis",
      "Cricket",
      "Golf"
    ]
  },
    
];

